<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on PACE research group</title>
    <link>https://paceiap.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on PACE research group</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; fdzoom, 2023 </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:10:22 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://paceiap.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FY-4A AGRI AOD (2018, 5min)</title>
      <link>https://paceiap.github.io/project/transferlearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:10:22 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paceiap.github.io/project/transferlearning/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The dataset is a colltection of FY-4A REGC AGRI AOD retrieved with transfer learning method (see details in the paper:A deep-learning and transfer-learning hybrid aerosol retrieval algorithm for FY4-AGRI: Development and verification over Asia). The AGRI AOD is built with 5min/4km. The dataset in this category is provided in 1 hour.&#xA;Due to the cloud mask before March 12th being derived from a simplified empirical algorithm, there is a difference in data quality between the AOD data before and after March 12th.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://paceiap.github.io/project/widelearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 16:10:22 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://paceiap.github.io/project/widelearning/</guid>
      <description>First estimation of high-resolution solar photovoltaic resource maps over China with Fengyun-4A satellite and machine learning Abstract Fengyun-4A (FY-4A), which is the latest-generation Chinese geostationary meteorological satellite, measures solar reflection and thermal emission with high temporal, spatial, and spectral resolutions. It is expected to be highly beneficial for solar resource assessment and forecasting in China. This study is the first to estimate, using FY-4A and a random forest model, the global horizontal irradiance (GHI) at a 4-km–15-min spatio-temporal resolution over China, as a means to arrive at a solar photovoltaic (PV) resource map.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
